shipt.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Shipt Same Day Delivery

Shipt, Inc. maintains two separate privacy policies, applicable to its Members and Shoppers.  Shipt’s Services are used by members, whom have subscribed to the Shipt membership service and are enabled to order and receive product delivery through use of the Shipt platform (“Members”), and shoppers, to whom Shipt provides Shipt Technology Services (as defined in the applicable agreement between Shipt and each shopper) and are enabled to accept Member orders, shop for and deliver products to Members (“Shoppers”). To the extent an individual is both a Member and a Shopper, the Services being utilized will determine the applicable privacy policy. 

  * Member Privacy Policy
  * Shopper Privacy Policy

**Shipt, Inc.  
****Member Privacy Policy  
****[Effective Date: April 5, 2019; Prior Update: July 16, 2016]**

### **Introduction**

Thank you for using Shipt! Shipt, Inc. (“Shipt”) values our Members and we recognize the importance of making sure you know how we handle your information. Our Member Privacy Policy explains: (1) what information we collect; (2) how we use it; (3) how we may share it; (4) how we protect it; and (5) what choices we offer.

### **When this Privacy Policy Applies**

This Member Privacy Policy applies to Shipt’s data collection during use of our shopping platform and delivery services, including [www.shipt.com](http://www.shipt.com/), the Shipt mobile application, and other Shipt-related sites, mobile applications, communications, capabilities and services (“Services”).  By using the Services, you signify your acceptance of this Member Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Member Privacy Policy, do not use the Services.  We may change or add to our Member Privacy Policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically.  

Our Member Privacy Policy does not apply to sites linked from our Services or to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you. Our Member Privacy Policy also does not cover the information practices of other companies or individuals who advertise our Services.

### **Information We Collect**

As part of the Services, various information is collected from you, through automated collection, and from third party sources.  Examples of when information, including personal information, is collected include: 

  * Form completion;
  * Account registration or updates;
  * Identity verification;
  * Access or use of the Services (e.g., place orders, search for products, pay for orders);
  * Communications with Shipt; and
  * SMS communications between a Member and a Shipt Shopper that are made using the Services.

We may combine or associate information we collect. We use the term “personal information” to refer to any information that identifies or can be used to identify you. Common examples of personal information include: full name, home address, email address, and phone number. Please note that if you choose not to provide us with information, your ability to use our Services may be limited.

#### Information You Give to Us

You may choose to provide us with information (including Personal Information) about yourself, such as your name, home address or other physical addresses you may select to associate with your account, email, phone number, date of birth, zip or postal code, user name and password, and payment card information. This type of information is typically collected when completing forms on our platform, placing orders, or communicating with Shipt.  You may also choose to submit to Shipt the email address of individuals whom you believe may be interested in becoming a Member – you are responsible for ensuring the submission of these emails are appropriate and permissible.

You may choose to use the interactive and social features that Shipt offers, which permit you to access the Services, submit content and communicate with Shipt.  Doing so provides Shipt with information such as name, e-mail address, and public profile information. Please note that when you post information in these interactive and social features, the content may be publicly accessible or accessible to other users.

#### Information We Obtain from Your Use of Our Services

When you use our Services, either through your internet browser or the mobile app, we collect certain information automatically, such as your internet protocol address, device identifier, operating system version, browser type, internet service provider, location, clickstream data, and details of how you use the Services (e.g., search terms, pages visited). 

**Geo-Location.**  For location information, we may collect and process general information (e.g., zip code) and information that is more specific (e.g., GPS-based functionality on mobile devices used to access the platform or specific features of the platform).  If you do not want your mobile device to provide us with location tracking information when you access the platform, then please follow the instructions in the “Your Choices” section below. 

**Cookies and Similar Technologies.** We and our partners use various technologies to automatically collect and store information when you interact with or use our Services, including use of cookies, web beacons, mobile SDKs or similar technologies.

  * _Cookies. When you access our Services, Shipt will issue a cookie to your device.  A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Services. _
  * _Web Beacons. Certain webpages maintained by Shipt, as well as emails sent by Shipt, may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that collect information about page visits and email viewing. Information collected may include limited personal information, such as name, email, and universal ID._
  * _Mobile Device Identifiers and SDKs. Shipt collects information from its mobile application users through deployment of mobile SDKs. A mobile SDK is the mobile app version of a web beacon (see “Web Beacons” above). The SDK is a bit of computer code that app developers can include in their apps to enable ads to be shown, data to be collected, and related services or analytics to be performed._

We also use these technologies to collect and store information when you interact with services from our partners, such as advertising and analytics. We may use this technology to deliver or help our partners deliver interest-based advertising (also known as online behavioral advertising) through mobile applications and browsers based on how you browse and shop online. If you’d like to opt-out from having ads tailored to you in this way, please follow the instructions in the “Your Choices” section below.

**Do Not Track Policy.** Some browsers have a ”do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser ”do not track” signals.

### **How We Use Information We Collect**

Examples of how we use the information we collect include:

  * Supporting the shopping and delivery process, including fulfilling orders, processing payment, verifying eligibility to buy certain products, communicating with Shoppers and providing customer service to users;
  * Authorizing access to our Services;
  * Providing Members with personalized Services; 
  * Sending service, support and administrative messages, reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and information requested by you, with such messages being conveyed via telephone, SMS, email, and other electronic message channels. 
  * Administering and communicating about referral programs and memberships, rewards, surveys, sweepstakes, contest, or other promotional activities or events sponsored or managed by Shipt, its parent companies, subsidiaries, and affiliates, and/or our third party business partners; 
  * Sending marketing, advertising, and promotional messages and other information that may be of interest, including information about Shipt, the Services, or general promotions for partner campaigns and services;
  * Understanding how users interact with our Services, including which web pages you visit at our website, which website you visited before coming to our website, and where you go after you leave our website;
  * Maintaining, improving, and optimizing our Services as well as develop new services;
  * Complying with legal requirements, including responding to subpoenas and search warrants; and
  * Protecting Shipt and/or its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, retail partners, Members, Shoppers, and the general public,  including investigation of possible fraud, theft, violations of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy, misuses of our Services, and/or attempts to harm Shipt and/or its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, retail partners, other Members or Shoppers, or any individual. 

### **Information We Share**

We share information with organizations and individuals outside of Shipt in the following circumstances:

  * **With Your Consent.** We will share information when we have your consent or when you have directed us to do so.  
  * **For Business Reasons.  **We provide information to our service providers and contractors who help us provide the Services or otherwise operate our business—this sharing includes appropriate instructions and contractual language for how the information can be used and how it should be protected.  We may share information with the merchants who fulfill the orders you place using our Services for their operational and marketing purposes. We may share information with our marketing partners. We may share information between and among Shipt, its parent companies, affiliates, and subsidiaries **.   **
  * **Behavioral Information.**  We may share behavioral information (including personal information and usage data) that we have collected about you in accordance with this Member Privacy Policy with our third party advertising partners, to permit such third parties to deliver advertisements when you visit other websites or mobile applications. This information is used to tailor online advertisements to your perceived interests (based on the behavioral information collected about you) and to provide advertising-related services such as reporting, attribution, analytics, and market research. You may be able to stop receipt of advertising in accordance with DAA and NAI opt-out mechanisms, as further described in the “Your Online Ad Choices” section of this Member Privacy Policy.
  * **Non-Personal and Aggregate Site Use Information.** We may share non-personal information (including, but not limited to, order and delivery details but not including payment card information) or aggregated, anonymized, or de-identified Personal Information with any third party, without restriction.
  * **For Legal Reasons.** We will share information if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 
    * Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
    * Enforce applicable Terms of Service including investigation of potential violations;
    * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or
    * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Shipt, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * **Business Transfers**. If we establish a new related entity, are acquired by or merged with another organization, or if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another organization, information about our users may be a transferred business asset.

### **How You Can Access and Update Your Information**

You may update or correct information about yourself by making changes in your account or emailing us at privacy@shipt.com.  Note that if you completely delete all such information or if you delete Services-critical information such as name or address, then your account will become deactivated.  We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law, to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements or for other legitimate business purposes.  

We may contact you to request that you update your information to ensure its integrity for the purposes of ongoing data management.

#### **Your Choices**

  *     * **Email.  **At any time, you can opt out of marketing and other emails by following the unsubscribe link provided in emailed offers, newsletters or other messages.  You will still receive operational emails such as order confirmation or other service-related emails.
    * **Push Notifications.**  You may opt-out from receiving push notifications from the Shipt mobile application by adjusting the permissions on your mobile device. This opt-out does not apply to in-app notifications.
    * **Geo-Location _._**  A Member may prevent the Member’s mobile device from sharing location data by adjusting the permissions on your mobile device.

  * **Web Site Analytics.**  Analytics services such as Google Analytics provide services that analyze information regarding visits to our websites and mobile applications. They use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking mechanisms to collect this information (see “Cookies and Similar Technologies” in this Privacy Policy for more).  To learn more about Google’s privacy practices, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). To access and use the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

#### Third Party Links

Shipt’s shopping platform, including its website and mobile application, may contain links to webpages operated by parties other than Shipt. We do not control such websites and are not responsible for their contents or the privacy policies or other practices of such websites. Our inclusion of links to such websites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such websites or any association with their operators. These websites and services may have their own privacy policies, which the user will be subject to upon linking to the third party’s website. Shipt strongly recommends that users review the third party’s terms and policies.

#### **How We Protect Personal Information**

Shipt maintains administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the user’s personal information and other information against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.  When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. 

#### **Children**

The Services are not intended for use by children.  We do not intentionally gather personal Information online about visitors who are under the age of 13.  If a child has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us to have the information deleted from our records. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us at privacy@shipt.com. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.  

#### **California Privacy Rights**

Under the California “Shine the Light” law, California residents are entitled to contact us to opt-out of disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may choose to opt-out of the sharing of your personal information with third parties for marketing purposes at any time by submitting a request to [privacy@shipt.com](about:blank). California users may request further information about our compliance with this law by contacting us at [privacy@shipt.com](mailto:privacy@shipt.com) or by writing to us at the address listed in the “How to Contact Us” section.

#### **Nevada Residents**

Nevada law gives Nevada consumers the right to request that a company not sell their personal information. This right applies even if their personal information is not currently being sold. If you are a Nevada resident and wish to exercise this right, please submit your request by emailing [privacy@shipt.com](about:blank). Please allow up to 60 days for a response.

#### **How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us in one of the following ways:

  * Send e-mail to: [privacy@shipt.com](mailto:privacy@shipt.com)
  * Send mail to our address:

**Shipt  
**Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry  
17 20th St. N Unit 100  
Birmingham, AL 35203

**Shipt, Inc.  
****Shopper Privacy Policy  
****[Effective Date: April 5, 2019]**

### **Introduction**

Thank you for being a Shipt Shopper! Shipt, Inc. (“Shipt”) values our Shoppers and we recognize the importance of making sure you know how we handle your information. Our Shopper Privacy Policy explains: (1) what information we collect; (2) how we use it; (3) how we may share it; and (4) how we protect it. 

### **When this Privacy Policy Applies**

The Shopper Privacy Policy applies to Shipt’s data collection occurring during a Shopper’s use of our shopping platform and delivery services, including the Shipt Shopper mobile application, and other Shipt-related sites, mobile applications, communications, capabilities and services (“Technology Services”).  By using the Technology Services, you signify your acceptance of the Shopper Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Shopper Privacy Policy, do not use the Technology Services. We may change or add to our Shopper Privacy Policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically.  

Our Shopper Privacy Policy does not apply to sites linked from our Technology Services or to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you. Our Shopper Privacy Policy also does not cover the information practices of other companies or individuals who advertise our Technology Services.

### **Information We Collect**

To become a Shopper, you are required to provide us with information (including Personal Information) about yourself.  We use the term “Personal Information” to refer to any information that identifies or can be used to identify you. Common examples of Personal Information we collect include: full name, home address, email address, phone number, date of birth, zip code, and a photograph. Examples of when information is collected include:  

  * Shopper application (including background check);
  * Identity verification;
  * Access or use of the Technology Services (e.g., using the Shipt Shopper mobile application to accept and execute orders);
  * Communications with Shipt; and
  * SMS communications between a Shopper and a Member that are made using the Technology Services.

In addition, when you use our Technology Services, we collect certain information automatically, such as your device identifier, location and details of how you use the Technology Services. 

#### **Geo-Location**  

For location information, we may collect and process both general information (e.g., zip code) and specific information (e.g., GPS-based functionality on mobile devices used to access the platform or specific features of the platform).  Shoppers must enable location tracking to access and use shopping functionalities, as relating real-time Shopper location to shopping and delivery locations is a key function of the Shipt platform. 

### **How We Use Information We Collect**

Examples of how we use the information we collect include:

  * Authorizing access to the Technology Services;
  * Facilitate communication between Members and Shoppers concerning order and delivery details and status updates;
  * Sending service, support and administrative messages, reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and information requested by Shoppers, with such messages being conveyed via telephone, SMS, email, and other electronic message channels;
  * Maintaining, improving, and optimizing our Technology Services as well as developing new features and functionality for the Technology Services;
  * Complying with legal requirements, including responding to subpoenas and search warrants; and
  * Protecting Shipt and/or its parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries, retail partners, Members, and the general public, including investigation of possible fraud, theft, violations of this Shopper Privacy Policy and misuses of our Technology Services.

### **Information We Share**

We share information with organizations and individuals outside of Shipt in the following circumstances:

  * **With Your Consent.** We will share information when we have your consent or when you have directed us to do so. Please note further instances of personal information disclosure may be set forth in the applicable agreement between each Shopper and Shipt.
  * **For Business Reasons.  **We provide information to our service providers and contractors who help us provide the Technology Services or otherwise operate our business **.  **
  * **For Legal Reasons.** We will share information if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:
    * Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
    * Enforce the applicable Shopper agreement, including investigation of potential violations; or
    * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * **Protection**. If Shipt has reasonable grounds to believe the Shopper has engaged or may engage in behavior that damages or threatens the rights, property, or safety of (i) Shipt, or any associated employee or agent, (ii) Shipt’s parent companies or a Shipt affiliate or subsidiary, or any associated employee or agent, (iii) any Member or Shopper, (iv) a Shipt retail partner, or (v) any other third-party, Shipt reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to provide information collected to third-parties and/or law enforcement, including personal identification and/or order history.
  * **Business Transfers**. If we establish a new related entity, are acquired by or merged with another organization, or if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another organization, information about our Shoppers may be a transferred business asset.

### **How We Protect Personal Information**

Shipt maintains administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the Shopper’s personal information and other information against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.  When we collect or transmit sensitive information, such as a Shopper bank account number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. 

### **How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about this Shopper Privacy Policy, you can contact us in one of the following ways:

  * Send e-mail to: [privacy@shipt.com](mailto:privacy@shipt.com)
  * Send mail to our address:

**Shipt  
**Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry  
17 20th St. N Unit 100  
Birmingham, AL 35203

Live Chat
